export default data = [
  {
      question: "Because Mr. Chang has been busy these days, it's ______ whether he will come to the party",
      options: ["unlikely","impossible","doubtful","inevitable"],
      correct_option: "doubtful"
  },
  {
      question: "I'm quite ______ to the weather in Taiwan, so I think I'll stay here for another year",
      options: ["devoted","satisfied","pleased","accustomed"],
      correct_option: "accustomed"
  },
  {
      question: "Mr. Smith won't tolerate talking during class; he says it ______ others",
      options: ["disturbs","deserves","destroys","dismisses"],
      correct_option: "disturbs"
  },
  {
      question: "On the basis of the clues, can you predict the ______ of the story?",
      options: ["outcome","headline","cause","performance"],
      correct_option: "outcome"
  },
  {
      question: "A good reader can often figure out what new words mean by using ______",
      options: ["contact","context","content","contest"],
      correct_option: "context"
  },
  {
      question: "I wonder why she ______ turned up the radio when I was studying",
      options: ["sympathetically","primarily","deliberately","thoroughly"],
      correct_option: "deliberately"
  },
  {
      question: "It suddenly ______ me that I had to get to the airport to meet a friend",
      options: ["took","struck","occurred","surprised"],
      correct_option: "struck"
  },
  {
      question: "Being a very careful person, he is quite ______ in giving his comments",
      options: ["reserved","melancholy","complicated","generous"],
      correct_option: "reserved"
  },
  {
      question: "Most viewers agreed that the movie ______ was not as good as the book",
      options: ["routine","version","copy","issue"],
      correct_option: "version"
  },
  {
      question: "The native greeted the travelers in a ______ language which was strange to them",
      options: ["contrary","relative","peculiar","spiral"],
      correct_option: "peculiar"
  },
]
